[GROANS] She slapped me
really hard...
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[HANNAH] He smells so good!
Like freshly brewed coffee!
[GIGGLING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
I'll go get more ice.
(In Korean) Thank you!
[GIGGLING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SLAPS]
- Ouch!
Hannah,
that's not why you're here!
Stop messing around!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are the pockets
in this thing?!
[JACKET FLAPPING]
You think I'm stupid?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, please,
you don't understand!
I need that!
That's very important!
My mother...
operation money...
please, sir?
Tell me how you got this.
Why?
It's confidential.
Well, I won't tell you then.
Then say goodbye
to your necklace.
Hey, just because you're tall
doesn't mean I won't fight back!
- [GRUNTS]
- Come and get it!
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Babe!
I'm home!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
Who the hell is this girl?!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]